Stoneacre
Can I
我可以吗
Peel a tomato
番茄去皮
I'm wondering if there's a tool here that I could use
我想知道这里是否有可以使用的工具
AutoTrader
How to be a better way to do this is looks like
看起来如何成为更好的方法
No
没有
Cured
治愈
Ok I'm gonna start from the butt
好吧，我将从屁股开始
The guard
守卫
Let's just call it quits
让我们称之为退出
Easier way to the door
轻松上门
How do people pee
人们如何撒尿
Tomatoes
番茄
Can a tattoo do
纹身可以吗
Straight out of fridge
直接从冰箱出来
So I may just this very quickly
所以我可能很快
Glenshane
Is really quickly seeing up a fruit or a vegetable and then shocking in a bath of ice water
真的很快发现水果或蔬菜，然后在冰水浴中震惊
First make an X in the bottom of the tomato
首先在番茄底部打一个X
What exercise is it a while similar boiling water
什么运动类似沸水一会儿
And another like a little tabs that you pull back
另一个像你拉回的小标签
I'm in year 4
我在四年级
A minute
一分钟
What's the inside of metal gates
金属门的内部是什么
I'm literally just on the phone
我只是在打电话
Ice water
冰水
Scanner app
扫描仪应用
There goes
有去
Is like picking glue off your fingers
就像从手指上摘下胶水一样
Portimao
波尔蒂芒
Naked now
现在裸体
On television
在电视上
Deadpool 2
死侍2
I'm going to branch
我要去分店
First thing I do is take my tomato and take the car
我要做的第一件事就是拿番茄去开车
I'm just going to call it
我只是称呼它
To stick the knife in take the core out and it's cool
插入刀把芯取出，很酷
Recording Astoria to the Peel comes off easily after whiplash
鞭打后轻松将Astoria录制到Peel
So they wanted to be in a full rolling boil a dropping in there have a little bit of tomato showing
因此，他们希望将其完全炸开，然后滴入一滴番茄
Is all roll around ok it's only going to go in there for about 30 seconds
一切都好吗，只去那里大约30秒钟
What I'm looking for is that you start to see if the skin will start to peel
我正在寻找的是，您开始看看皮肤是否会开始脱落
IKEA is not a cooker to me that you don't want to cook it you just want to loosen the skin
宜家对我来说不是炊具，因为您不想煮它，只是想让皮肤松弛
So this point I'm going to take it out the water the boiler working tonight then stopped working
所以这点我要把它从锅炉今晚的水里拿出来，然后停止工作
Opens a nice person leave this on the corner that continued
打开一个好人，把这个留在继续的角落
So now they're taking my tomato out of the boiling water and it's early chill
所以现在他们把我的西红柿从沸水中拿走了，现在很冷
Can you give me
你能给我吗
I get a paring knife
我有一把削皮刀
I grab a little bit of the skin
我抓住一点皮肤
And peel back
然后剥回来
The skin comes right off
皮肤马上脱落
Super
超
And that appeal to me
那对我的吸引力
A little basket
一个小篮子
A snotty nose rather than the Eminem